I want to think I have you but I don't like to lie
So I lie here while you lie to her
Want to think you have me cause you don't like to lose
But you lose me like they always do
Think I know you better, better to forget her
Certain people made for running
Think I need you more than, let you know I'm golden
Tell me this means more than nothing
All you say is black roses, could've been but that's all
Don't ask for something more than yours
All you say is black roses
All you say is black roses, could've been but that's all
Want to think I have you but I don't like to lie
So I lie here while you lie to her
Think I know you better, better to forget her
Certain people made for running
Think I need you more than, let you know I'm golden
Tell me this means more than nothing
All you say is black roses, could've been but that's all
Don't ask for something more than yours
All you say is black roses
All you say is black roses, could've been but that's all